Dilay Işık KİRİŞÇİ

Frontend Developer

hlinkedin.com/in/dilay-kirisci-65baa8152/ isik_kirisci@gmail.com +905544359872 https://github.com/DilayKirisci





Highly motivated to work as a Frontend Developer, where I can demonstrate my analytical, technical and programming skills and use my knowledge and experience to contribute to the company and clients to achieve their goals.

Work Experience



English Language Instructor

• Baskent Universitesi (2021-2023)

English Language Teacher

• Bahcesehir Schools (2019-2020)

English Language Teacher

• Canada Schools (2017-2019)

Education History



Ph.D. Pamukkale University

Foreign Language Education (2021-)

M.A. Bahcesehir University

• Foreign Language Education (2019-2021)

B.A. Boğaziçi University

• Foreign Language Education (2012-2017)

Relevant Skills

- HTML
- Css and Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Git/ Github

Interest

- Swimming
- Jogging
- Cycling

Languages

- Turkish (native)
- English (C1)

References

• Kaan Sari

Lead Developer at Cormind

Vicdan Yalcin

Frontend Developler at Hawk al